A Guide to the Dudley S. Ingraham Papers 1980.0036
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
Dudley S. Ingraham Papers
1849-1984
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1980.0036
30.5 Linear Feet
Dudley Seymour Ingraham, son of William S. and Grace Seymour Ingraham, was born in Bristol, Connecticut on 14 August 1890. He was the great-grandson of Elias Ingraham, founder of the E. Ingraham Company (1831), manufacturer of clocks and watches. Ingraham attended local school and entered Phillips Andover Academy in 1906. In 1913 he graduated from Cornell University with a Bachelor of Law degree. He joined the family firm as a billing clerk and worked his way up to director, vice-president, treasurer and president. He retired on 23 August 1956, the last family member to hold the position of president. Dudley S. Ingraham died 23 March 1982 in Sanibal Island, Florida.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Organization
Series I: Correspondence (1901-1984) contains personal and business correspondence. Files contain correspondence with charitable, civic and business organizations including the Bristol Boys Club, Board of Education, Community Chest, Bristol Hospital, Chamber of Commerce, First Congregational Church, Salvation Army and the Boy Scouts of America. The correspondence also includes confirmation of personal engagements, events and acknowledgments of business orders, as well as communication between various family members. Recent additions have included the correspondence of Kay Seymour, Ingraham's romantic interest in the mid-1970s. The series is arranged chronologically.
Series II: Personal Papers (1849-1976) includes assorted papers and attachments pertaining to personal affairs. Included are bills, clippings, photographs, financial and legal papers. There is some overlap between Series I and II pertaining to civic organizations.
Series III: Company Records (1921-1964) materials relate to Ingraham's long association with the family business and include minutes, reports, statistics, advertisements, catalogs, blueprints and memoranda.
Series IV: Anna Ingraham Estate (1920-1957) contains correspondence and materials pertaining to the affairs of his aunt, Anna Ingraham (wife of Irving Ingraham). While Anna lived in Europe, Ingraham assisted in handling her extensive financial and legal affairs in the United States. Ingraham served as executor of the estate.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by broad subject area.
Biography
Dudley Seymour Ingraham, son of William S. and Grace Seymour Ingraham, was born in Bristol, Connecticut on 14 August 1890. He was the great-grandson of Elias Ingraham, founder of the E. Ingraham Company (1831), manufacturer of clocks and watches. Ingraham attended local schools and entered Phillips Andover Academy in 1906. In 1913, he graduated from Cornell University with a Bachelor of Law degree. In 1920, he married Marion Morton, with whom he had four children--Seymour, Joseph, Dudley, Jr. and Robert. Following the death of his wife in 1941, Ingraham married Helga Jetinsky, with whom he had one daughter, Laura.
After graduation, Ingraham joined the family firm as a billing clerk. Following a two year period of service in the United State Army during World War I, Ingraham returned to the company and was involved in many facets of operations, including purchasing, legal affairs and sales. In May 1927, he was elected director and vice-president of the E. Ingraham Company. Mr. Ingraham also served as treasurer from 1931 until 1954. Along with his brother, Edward Ingraham II, he managed the affairs of the company for almost thirty years. On 8 April 1954, he succeeded Edward as president and served in that post until 23 August 1956, the last family member to hold the position of president.
Mr. Ingraham also served as a director and vice president of the Bristol Savings Bank, a director of the Bristol Bank and Trust Company, a member of the Bristol Brass Corporation's Board of Directors and president of the Georgica Association of Wainscott, (L.I.) New York.
Ingraham was active in numerous civic and religious affairs in Bristol serving as a member of the following organizations: Bristol Boys Club, Board of Education, Community Chest, Bristol Hospital, Chamber of Commerce and the First Congregational Church. An active member of the Boy Scouts since 1940, he received numerous awards and served on several local and national scout committees.
Dudley S. Ingraham died 23 March 1982 in Sanibal Island, Florida.
Acquisition Information
The Dudley S. Ingraham Papers, along with the records of the E. Ingraham Company, were donated to Yale University Library by Mr. Ingraham and the company in November 1961. Additional items were added in 1965.
Scope and Content
The Dudley S. Ingraham Papers, along with the Edward Ingraham Papers and the E. Ingraham Company Records, form a basic source of the history of clockmaking in the United States. Additional information on special topics such as labor unions and tariffs and, to a lesser extent, the history of Bristol, Connecticut is also present in the collection.
Mr. Ingraham's correspondence forms the largest portion of the collection. The letters document not only the actions of the E. Ingraham Company but also the interactions of the various members of the Ingraham family. A limited genealogical chart is included in the paper copy of the finding aid to assist researchers in identifying the familial relationships between the correspondents represented in the collection.
Separated Material
Photographs have been placed in the Photograph Collection--MSS1980-0036.
Bristol Hospital, Inc. Rules and Regulations (effective January 27, 1959). Dodd WRA 3
Bristol Hospital, Inc. Thirty-sixth Annual Report of the Bristol Hospital, Inc. for the year ending September 30, 1956. 1956. Dodd WRA 4
Foxhollow School for Girls. Foxhollow. c. 1971. Dodd XA I.12 no. 49
Foxhollow School for Girls. Foxhollow Alumnae Bulletin. V. 3, #1, 4 (1959-1960); V. 4, #1 (1961). Dodd Periodicals
Alumnae Association of Foxhollow School. Directory. 1964. Dodd Periodicals
Harold F. Emmett Post, No. 994, Veterans of Foreign Wars. The Poppy. V. 2, #1, 1925. Dodd Periodicals
My Country Society, Inc.. My Country. V. 16, #1, Spring 1982. Dodd Periodicals
The Cornellian Council. The Solution. 1925. Dodd XA II.2 no. 110
State of New York. Temporary State Commission on Protection and Preservation of the Atlantic Shore Front. The Protection and Preservation of the Atlantic Shore Front of the State of New York. Supplement to Final Report. Adopted July 27, 1962. Dodd XA I.12 no. 41
Hurricane Memorial Booklet: September 21, 1938. 1938. Dodd XA I.12 no. 22
Manuscripts (document genre); Personal papers; Financial Records; Clocks and watches; Administrative records; Photographs; Connecticut (state); Notebooks; Minutes (administrative records); Blueprints (reprographic copies).; Bristol (inhabited place); Publications (documents); United States (nation); Correspondence; Clock and watch industry; E. Ingraham Company; Ingraham
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1901-1984
  General note
  Correspondence for which a year can be indentified but not a month have been placed in the January folder for that year. Correspondence for which a year cannot be indentified have been placed in 1:1--no date.
  - undated (Box 1:1)
  - 1901 (Box 1:2)
  - 1904 (Box 1:3)
  - 1906 (Box 1:4)
  - 1907 (Box 1:5)
  - 1908 (Box 1:6)
  - 1909 (Box 1:7)
  - 1910 (Box 1:8)
  - 1911 (Box 1:9)
  - 1912 January - May (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1912 June - December (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1913 (Box 2:12)
  - 1915-1916 (Box 2:13)
  - 1917 (Box 2:14)
  - 1918 (Box 2:15)
  - 1919 January - March (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1919 April - May (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - June - October, 1919 (Box 3:18)
  - November - December, 1919 (Box 3:19)
  - January - March, 1920 (Box 3:20)
  - April - June, 1920 (Box 3:21)
  - July - September, 1920 (Box 3:22)
  - October - December, 1920 (Box 3:23)
  - January - August, 1921 (Box 3:24)
  - September, 1921 (Box 3:25)
  - October, 1921 (Box 3:26)
  - January, 1922 (Box 3:27)
  - 1922 February (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1922 March (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - April, 1922 (Box 4:30)
  - May, 1922 (Box 4:31)
  - June, 1922 (Box 4:32)
  - July, 1922 (Box 4:33)
  - August, 1922 (Box 4:34)
  - September - December, 1922 (Box 4:35)
  - 1923 (Box 4:36)
  - 1924 (Box 4:37)
  - January, 1925 (Box 4:38)
  - February, 1925 (Box 4:39)
  - March, 1925 (Box 4:40)
  - April, 1925 (Box 4:41)
  - May, 1925 (Box 4:42)
  - 1925 June (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 1925 July (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - August, 1925 (Box 5:45)
  - September, 1925 (Box 5:46)
  - October, 1925 (Box 5:47)
  - November, 1925 (Box 5:48)
  - December, 1925 (Box 5:49)
  - January, 1926 (Box 5:50)
  - February, 1926 (Box 5:51)
  - March, 1926 (Box 5:52)
  - April, 1926 (Box 5:53)
  - May, 1926 (Box 5:54)
  - 1926 June (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1926 July (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - August, 1926 (Box 6:57)
  - September, 1926 (Box 6:58)
  - October, 1926 (Box 6:59)
  - November, 1926 (Box 6:60)
  - December, 1926 (Box 6:61)
  - January, 1927 (Box 6:62)
  - February, 1927 (Box 6:63)
  - March, 1927 (Box 6:64)
  - 1927 April (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 1927 May (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - June, 1927 (Box 7:67)
  - July, 1927 (Box 7:68)
  - August, 1927 (Box 7:69)
  - September, 1927 (Box 7:70)
  - October, 1927 (Box 7:71)
  - November, 1927 (Box 7:72)
  - December, 1927 (Box 7:73)
  - 1928 January (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - 1928 February (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - March, 1928 (Box 8:76)
  - April, 1928 (Box 8:77)
  - May, 1928 (Box 8:78)
  - June, 1928 (Box 8:79)
  - July, 1928 (Box 8:80)
  - August, 1928 (Box 8:81)
  - September, 1928 (Box 8:82)
  - October, 1928 (Box 8:83)
  - 1928 November (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - 1928 December (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - 1929 (Box 9:86)
  - January, 1930 (Box 9:87)
  - February, 1930 (Box 9:88)
  - March, 1930 (Box 9:89)
  - April, 1930 (Box 9:90)
  - May, 1930 (Box 9:91)
  - June, 1930 (Box 9:92)
  - July, 1930 (Box 9:93)
  - August, 1930 (Box 9:94)
  - September, 1930 (Box 9:95)
  - October, 1930 (Box 9:96)
  - November, 1930 (Box 9:97)
  - 1930 December (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - 1931 January (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - February 1931 (Box 10:100)
  - March 1931 (Box 10:101)
  - April 1931 (Box 10:102)
  - May 1931 (Box 10:103)
  - June 1931 (Box 10:104)
  - July 1931 (Box 10:105)
  - August 1931 (Box 10:106)
  - September 1931 (Box 10:107)
  - October 1931 (Box 10:108)
  - 1931 November (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - 1931 December (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - January, 1932 (Box 11:111)
  - February, 1932 (Box 11:112)
  - March, 1932 (Box 11:113)
  - April, 1932 (Box 11:114)
  - May, 1932 (Box 11:115)
  - June, 1932 (Box 11:116)
  - July, 1932 (Box 11:117)
  - 1932 August (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - 1932 September (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - October, 1932 (Box 12:120)
  - November, 1932 (Box 12:121)
  - December, 1932 (Box 12:122)
  - January, 1933 (Box 12:123)
  - February, 1933 (Box 12:124)
  - March, 1933 (Box 12:125)
  - April, 1933 (Box 12:126)
  - May, 1933 (Box 12:127)
  - 1933 June (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - 1933 July (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - August, 1933 (Box 13:130)
  - September, 1933 (Box 13:131)
  - October, 1933 (Box 13:132)
  - November, 1933 (Box 13:133)
  - December, 1933 (Box 13:134)
  - January, 1934 (Box 13:135)
  - February, 1934 (Box 13:136)
  - March, 1934 (Box 13:137)
  - 1934 April (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - 1934 May (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - June, 1934 (Box 14:140)
  - July, 1934 (Box 14:141)
  - August, 1934 (Box 14:142)
  - September, 1934 (Box 14:143)
  - October, 1934 (Box 14:144)
  - November, 1934 (Box 14:145)
  - December, 1934 (Box 14:146)
  - 1935 January (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - 1935 February (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - March, 1935 (Box 15:149)
  - April, 1935 (Box 15:150)
  - May, 1935 (Box 15:151)
  - June, 1935 (Box 15:152)
  - July, 1935 (Box 15:153)
  - August, 1935 (Box 15:154)
  - September, 1935 (Box 15:155)
  - October, 1935 (Box 15:156)
  - November, 1935 (Box 15:157)
  - December, 1935 (Box 15:158)
  - 1936 January (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - 1936 February (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - March, 1936 (Box 16:161)
  - April, 1936 (Box 16:162)
  - May, 1936 (Box 16:163)
  - June, 1936 (Box 16:164)
  - July, 1936 (Box 16:165)
  - August, 1936 (Box 16:166)
  - September, 1936 (Box 16:167)
  - October, 1936 (Box 16:168)
  - November, 1936 (Box 16:169)
  - 1936 December (Box 17, Folder 170)
  - 1937 January (Box 17, Folder 171)
  - 1937 February (Box 17, Folder 172)
  - March, 1937 (Box 17:173)
  - April, 1937 (Box 17:174)
  - May, 1937 (Box 17:175)
  - June, 1937 (Box 17:176)
  - July, 1937 (Box 17:177)
  - August, 1937 (Box 17:178)
  - September, 1937 (Box 17:179)
  - October, 1937 (Box 17:180)
  - November, 1937 (Box 17:181)
  - December, 1937 (Box 17:182)
  - 1938 January (Box 18, Folder 183)
  - 1938 February (Box 18, Folder 184)
  - March, 1938 (Box 18:185)
  - April, 1938 (Box 18:186)
  - May, 1938 (Box 18:187)
  - June, 1938 (Box 18:188)
  - July - August, 1938 (Box 18:189)
  - September, 1938 (Box 18:190)
  - October, 1938 (Box 18:191)
  - November, 1938 (Box 18:192)
  - December, 1938 (Box 18:193)
  - January, 1939 (Box 18:194)
  - February, 1939 (Box 18:195)
  - March, 1939 (Box 18:196)
  - 1939 April (Box 19, Folder 197)
  - 1939 May (Box 19, Folder 198)
  - June, 1939 (Box 19:199)
  - July, 1939 (Box 19:200)
  - August, 1939 (Box 19:201)
  - September, 1939 (Box 19:202)
  - October, 1939 (Box 19:203)
  - November, 1939 (Box 19:204)
  - December, 1939 (Box 19:205)
  - January, 1940 (Box 19:206)
  - February, 1940 (Box 19:207)
  - March, 1940 (Box 19:208)
  - April, 1940 (Box 19:209)
  - May, 1940 (Box 19:210)
  - 1940 June (Box 20, Folder 211)
  - 1940 July (Box 20, Folder 212)
  - August, 1940 (Box 20:213)
  - September, 1940 (Box 20:214)
  - October, 1940 (Box 20:215)
  - November, 1940 (Box 20:216)
  - December, 1940 (Box 20:217)
  - January, 1941 (Box 20:218)
  - February, 1941 (Box 20:219)
  - March, 1941 (Box 20:220)
  - April, 1941 (Box 20:221)
  - 1941 May (Box 21, Folder 222)
  - Condolences for Marion, 1941 May (Box 21, Folder 223)
  - June, 1941 (Box 21:224)
  - July, 1941 (Box 21:225)
  - August, 1941 (Box 21:226)
  - September, 1941 (Box 21:227)
  - October, 1941 (Box 21:228)
  - November, 1941 (Box 21:229)
  - December, 1941 (Box 21:230)
  - January, 1942 (Box 21:231)
  - February - March, 1942 (Box 21:232)
  - April, 1942 (Box 21:233)
  - May - June, 1942 (Box 21:234)
  - July, 1942 (Box 21:235)
  - 1942 August (Box 22, Folder 236)
  - 1942 September (Box 22, Folder 237)
  - October, 1942 (Box 22:238)
  - November, 1942 (Box 22:239)
  - December, 1942 (Box 22:240)
  - January, 1943 (Box 22:241)
  - February, 1943 (Box 22:242)
  - March, 1943 (Box 22:243)
  - April, 1943 (Box 22:244)
  - May, 1943 (Box 22:245)
  - June, 1943 (Box 22:246)
  - July, 1943 (Box 22:247)
  - August, 1943 (Box 22:248)
  - September, 1943 (Box 22:249)
  - 1943 October (Box 23, Folder 250)
  - 1943 November (Box 23, Folder 251)
  - December, 1943 December (Box 23, Folder 252)
  - January, 1944 (Box 23:253)
  - February, 1944 (Box 23:254)
  - March, 1944 (Box 23:255)
  - April, 1944 (Box 23:256)
  - May, 1944 (Box 23:257)
  - June, 1944 (Box 23:258)
  - July, 1944 (Box 23:259)
  - August, 1944 (Box 23:260)
  - September, 1944 (Box 23:261)
  - October, 1944 (Box 23:262)
  - November, 1944 (Box 23:263)
  - December, 1944 (Box 23:264)
  - January, 1945 (Box 23:265)
  - February - March, 1945 (Box 23:266)
  - 1945 April (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - 1945 May (Box 24, Folder 268)
  - June, 1945 (Box 24:269)
  - July, 1945 (Box 24:270)
  - August, 1945 (Box 24:271)
  - September, 1945 (Box 24:272)
  - October, 1945 (Box 24:273)
  - November, 1945 (Box 24:274)
  - December, 1945 (Box 24:275)
  - January, 1946 (Box 24:276)
  - February, 1946 (Box 24:277)
  - March, 1946 (Box 24:278)
  - April, 1946 (Box 24:279)
  - May, 1946 (Box 24:280)
  - 1946 June (Box 25, Folder 281)
  - 1946 July (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - August, 1946 (Box 25:283)
  - September, 1946 (Box 25:284)
  - October, 1946 (Box 25:285)
  - November - December, 1946 (Box 25:286)
  - January, 1947 (Box 25:287)
  - February, 1947 (Box 25:288)
  - March, 1947 (Box 25:289)
  - April, 1947 (Box 25:290)
  - May, 1947 (Box 25:291)
  - June, 1947 (Box 25:292)
  - July, 1947 (Box 25:293)
  - August, 1947 (Box 25:294)
  - September, 1947 (Box 25:295)
  - October, 1947 (Box 25:296)
  - 1947 November (Box 26, Folder 297)
  - 1947 December (Box 26, Folder 298)
  - January, 1948 (Box 26:299)
  - February, 1948 (Box 26:300)
  - March, 1948 (Box 26:301)
  - April, 1948 (Box 26:302)
  - May, 1948 (Box 26:303)
  - June, 1948 (Box 26:304)
  - July, 1948 (Box 26:305)
  - August, 1948 (Box 26:306)
  - September, 1948 (Box 26:307)
  - October, 1948 (Box 26:308)
  - November, 1948 (Box 26:309)
  - December, 1948 (Box 26:310)
  - January, 1949 (Box 26:311)
  - 1949 February (Box 27, Folder 312)
  - 1949 March (Box 27, Folder 313)
  - April, 1949 (Box 27:314)
  - May - June, 1949 (Box 27:315)
  - July - August, 1949 (Box 27:316)
  - September, 1949 (Box 27:317)
  - October, 1949 (Box 27:318)
  - November, 1949 (Box 27:319)
  - December, 1949 (Box 27:320)
  - January, 1950 (Box 27:321)
  - February, 1950 (Box 27:322)
  - March, 1950 (Box 27:323)
  - April, 1950 (Box 27:324)
  - May, 1950 (Box 27:325)
  - 1950 June (Box 28, Folder 326)
  - 1950 July (Box 28, Folder 327)
  - August, 1950 (Box 28:328)
  - September, 1950 (Box 28:329)
  - October, 1950 (Box 28:330)
  - November, 1950 (Box 28:331)
  - December, 1950 (Box 28:332)
  - January, 1951 (Box 28:333)
  - February, 1951 (Box 28:334)
  - March, 1951 (Box 28:335)
  - April, 1951 (Box 28:336)
  - May, 1951 (Box 28:337)
  - June, 1951 (Box 28:338)
  - July, 1951 (Box 28:339)
  - August, 1951 (Box 28:340)
  - September, 1951 (Box 28:341)
  - October, 1951 (Box 28:342)
  - November, 1951 (Box 29:343)
  - December, 1951 (Box 29:344)
  - January, 1952 (Box 29:345)
  - February, 1952 (Box 29:346)
  - March, 1952 (Box 29:347)
  - April, 1952 (Box 29:348)
  - May, 1952 (Box 29:349)
  - June, 1952 (Box 29:350)
  - July, 1952 (Box 29:351)
  - August, 1952 (Box 29:352)
  - September, 1952 (Box 29:353)
  - October, 1952 (Box 29:354)
  - November, 1952 (Box 29:355)
  - December, 1952 (Box 29:356)
  - January, 1953 (Box 29:357)
  - February, 1953 (Box 30:358)
  - March, 1953 (Box 30:359)
  - April, 1953 (Box 30:360)
  - May, 1953 (Box 30:361)
  - June, 1953 (Box 30:362)
  - July, 1953 (Box 30:363)
  - August, 1953 (Box 30:364)
  - September, 1953 (Box 30:365)
  - October, 1953 (Box 30:366)
  - November, 1953 (Box 30:367)
  - December, 1953 (Box 30:368)
  - January, 1954 (Box 30:369)
  - February, 1954 (Box 30:370)
  - March, 1954 (Box 30:371)
  - April, 1954 (Box 30:372)
  - May, 1954 (Box 30:373)
  - June, 1954 (Box 30:374)
  - July, 1954 (Box 30:375)
  - August, 1954 (Box 31:376)
  - September, 1954 (Box 31:377)
  - October, 1954 (Box 31:378)
  - November, 1954 (Box 31:379)
  - December, 1954 (Box 31:380)
  - January, 1955 (Box 31:381)
  - February, 1955 (Box 31:382)
  - March, 1955 (Box 31:383)
  - April, 1955 (Box 31:384)
  - May, 1955 (Box 31:385)
  - June, 1955 (Box 31:386)
  - July, 1955 (Box 31:387)
  - August, 1955 (Box 31:388)
  - September, 1955 (Box 31:389)
  - October, 1955 (Box 31:390)
  - November, 1955 (Box 31:391)
  - December, 1955 (Box 32:392)
  - January, 1956 (Box 32:393)
  - February - March, 1956 (Box 32:394)
  - April, 1956 (Box 32:395)
  - May, 1956 (Box 32:396)
  - June, 1956 (Box 32:397)
  - July - August, 1956 (Box 32:398)
  - September, 1956 (Box 32:399)
  - October, 1956 (Box 32:400)
  - November - December, 1956 (Box 32:401)
  - January, 1957 (Box 32:402)
  - February, 1957 (Box 32:403)
  - March, 1957 (Box 32:404)
  - April, 1957 (Box 32:405)
  - May, 1957 (Box 32:406)
  - June, 1957 (Box 32:407)
  - July - August, 1957 (Box 32:408)
  - September - October, 1957 (Box 33:409)
  - November, 1957 (Box 33:410)
  - December, 1957 (Box 33:411)
  - January, 1958 (Box 33:412)
  - February, 1958 (Box 33:413)
  - March, 1958 (Box 33:414)
  - April, 1958 (Box 33:415)
  - May, 1958 (Box 33:416)
  - June, 1958 (Box 33:417)
  - July - August, 1958 (Box 33:418)
  - September - October, 1958 (Box 33:419)
  - November, 1958 (Box 33:420)
  - December, 1958 (Box 33:421)
  - January - February, 1959 (Box 33:422)
  - March - April, 1959 (Box 33:423)
  - May, 1959 (Box 33:424)
  - June, 1959 (Box 33:425)
  - July - August, 1959 (Box 33:426)
  - September, 1959 (Box 33:427)
  - October, 1959 (Box 33:428)
  - November - December, 1959 (Box 34:429)
  - January, 1960 (Box 34:430)
  - February, 1960 (Box 34:431)
  - March, 1960 (Box 34:432)
  - April, 1960 (Box 34:433)
  - May, 1960 (Box 34:434)
  - June, 1960 (Box 34:435)
  - July - August, 1960 (Box 34:436)
  - September, 1960 (Box 34:437)
  - October, 1960 (Box 34:438)
  - November - December, 1960 (Box 34:439)
  - January - February, 1961 (Box 35:440)
  - March - April, 1961 (Box 35:441)
  - May - June, 1961 (Box 35:442)
  - July - August, 1961 (Box 35:443)
  - September - October, 1961 (Box 35:444)
  - November - December, 1961 (Box 35:445)
  - January - February, 1962 (Box 35:446)
  - March - April, 1962 (Box 35:447)
  - May - June, 1962 (Box 35:448)
  - July - October, 1962 (Box 35:449)
  - November - December, 1962 (Box 35:450)
  - January, 1963 (Box 36:451)
  - February, 1963 (Box 36:452)
  - March, 1963 (Box 36:453)
  - April - May, 1963 (Box 36:454)
  - June - August, 1963 (Box 36:455)
  - September - December, 1963 (Box 36:456)
  - January - April, 1964 (Box 36:457)
  - May - August, 1964 (Box 36:458)
  - September - December, 1964 (Box 36:459)
  - January, 1965 (Box 36:460)
  - February - March, 1965 (Box 36:461)
  - April, 1965 (Box 36:462)
  - May, 1965 (Box 36:463)
  - June, 1965 (Box 37:464)
  - July - August, 1965 (Box 37:465)
  - September, 1965 (Box 37:466)
  - October, 1965 (Box 37:467)
  - November, 1965 (Box 37:468)
  - December, 1965 (Box 37:469)
  - January, 1966 (Box 37:470)
  - February, 1966 (Box 37:471)
  - March, 1966 (Box 37:472)
  - April, 1966 (Box 37:473)
  - May, 1966 (Box 38:474)
  - June, 1966 (Box 38:475)
  - July, 1966 (Box 38:476)
  - August, 1966 (Box 38:477)
  - September, 1966 (Box 38:478)
  - October - November, 1966 (Box 38:479)
  - December, 1966 (Box 38:480)
  - January, 1967 (Box 38:481)
  - February, 1967 (Box 38:482)
  - March, 1967 (Box 38:483)
  - April - May, 1967 (Box 38:484)
  - June, 1967 (Box 38:485)
  - July - August, 1967 (Box 38:486)
  - September, 1967 (Box 38:487)
  - October, 1967 (Box 39:488)
  - November, 1967 (Box 39:489)
  - December, 1967 (Box 39:490)
  - January - February, 1968 (Box 39:491)
  - March, 1968 (Box 39:492)
  - April, 1968 (Box 39:493)
  - May, 1968 (Box 39:494)
  - June, 1968 (Box 39:495)
  - July, 1968 (Box 39:496)
  - August, 1968 (Box 39:497)
  - September, 1968 (Box 39:498)
  - October, 1968 (Box 39:499)
  - November - December, 1968 (Box 39:500)
  - January, 1969 (Box 39:501)
  - February - April, 1969 (Box 39:502)
  - May, 1969 (Box 40:503)
  - June - July, 1969 (Box 40:504)
  - August - September, 1969 (Box 40:505)
  - October, 1969 (Box 40:506)
  - November - December, 1969 (Box 40:507)
  - January - February, 1970 (Box 40:508)
  - March - April, 1970 (Box 40:509)
  - May, 1970 (Box 40:510)
  - June - July, 1970 (Box 40:511)
  - August - September, 1970 (Box 40:512)
  - October - December, 1970 (Box 40:513)
  - January, 1971 (Box 41:514)
  - February - April, 1971 (Box 41:515)
  - May - June, 1971 (Box 41:516)
  - July - August, 1971 (Box 41:517)
  - September - October, 1971 (Box 41:518)
  - November - December, 1971 (Box 41:519)
  - January - March, 1972 (Box 41:520)
  - April - May, 1972 (Box 41:521)
  - June - July, 1972 (Box 41:522)